

## CONTACT

- +353 87 94 30 328
- ✓ alan@mayweatherltd.com
- Meath | Ireland

# **EDUCATION**

#### Harvard University

Harvard Law School, Executive Education PON Global (Program on Negotiation) – 2018

Dublin Institute of Technology CPD Diploma, Print & Digital Media Tech Management – 2011–2013

Print Media Apprenticeship 2006–2010

# **KEY SKILLS**

- Strategic Leadership & Negotiation
- B2B Sales & Client
  Management
- M&A & Private Equity

# **ALAN CLARKE**

BUILDING REVENUE, RELATIONSHIPS & REPUTATION IN GLOBAL PARTNERSHIPS & STRATEGIC GROWTH

## PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Seasoned commercial leader with over 15 years' experience driving sales, negotiating strategic contracts, and leading high-impact operations and strategies in print media, manufacturing, and private equity. Proven track record of growing revenues from €500k to €9M+, leading international teams, and executing successful M&A strategies. Founder of Mayweather Ltd and experienced in organizing large-scale leadership events with high profile guest speakers through Mayweather's brand inXtremis.

## PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

#### inXtremis

Founder - (Jun 2022 - Present)

 Founded and manage a leadership and motivation event company Inxtremis. Planning and organizing events throughout EMEA.
 Organized events in Dublin, Dubai, and France with audiences of over 2,000 people featuring high-profile speakers such as David Goggins for the inaugural event and well-known Irish sports personalities for high-end luxury galas and motivational events from Paris to the UAE.
 Continuously measured and analyzed the impact of marketing efforts, adapting strategies to ensure alignment with business goals.

### Mayweather Ltd

Founder | CEO - (Jun 2021 - Present)

 Founded a private equity firm post-Colorman exit, focusing on strategic investments in startups and established businesses meeting certain criteria seeking growth. Crafted adaptable and efficient solutions that generated commercial value. Skilled in relationshipbuilding, negotiations, and identifying and developing opportunities leading to long-term value.

#### Colorman (Ireland) Limited

Commercial Director - (Jun 2017 - Jun 2021)

 Led pricing strategy, contract negotiations, and budgeting as a board member. Spearheaded expansion by successfully adding new Fortune 500 clients like Google, increasing personal sales to €9M annually. Visited U.S. clients bi-monthly to enhance service. Identified cost-saving opportunities via lean manufacturing and Six Sigma.

- Pricing Strategy & Budgeting
- Event Planning & Public
  Speaking
- Manufacturing & Print Technology
- Lean Manufacturing
- Project Management

commercial strategy. Colorman achieved €7M EBITDA on €30M turnover. Team member in negotiating the successful sale of Colorman at a 7× EBITDA multiple—well above the industry norm of 4-5×.

## Colorman (Ireland) Limited

Overseas Sales Manager - (Mar 2012 - Jun 2021)

• Expanded client accounts in the medical, pharmaceutical, and IT sectors, resulting in annual sales growth from €500K to €9M. Spearheaded new opportunities in personalized gift card solutions by recognizing client needs through strong relationships.

## Colorman (Ireland) Limited

Print Media Technician - (2006 - Jan 2011)

 Completed technical apprenticeship in print media. Gained deep expertise in print and packaging production and manufacturing processes.